## **Connor Shea**

https://connorshea.github.io connor.james.shea@gmail.com

With three years of experience in graphic design and one in web development, primarily working with HTML, CSS/SCSS, and JavaScript (jQuery/React.js), I have significant experience handling both the design and implementation of userfacing websites.

## **Work Experience**

# CO-FOUNDER, HEAD OF DESIGN / FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT, NOIDED MEDIA, LLC 2014 - PRESENT

- Co-founded Noided Media, LLC and serve as head designer and front-end developer for all products.
- ImageHex Designed the overall product experience, produced wireframes, mockups, and brand identity, and developed the site using Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS/SCSS, and JavaScript (jQuery).
- **Fiction Dock** With experience gained from developing ImageHex, Fiction Dock was used as a testbed for more advanced Ruby on Rails practices, including the addition of React.js to the tech stack. I lead the design and frontend development of the project.
- **WavHead** Conceptualized, designed, and developed the music player interface as well as the promotional website and graphics.

#### WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER, FREELANCE - 2014 - PRESENT

- I've worked as a freelance web developer for multiple clients, including:
  - FNA a small indie game engine powering games like Terraria, Fez.
  - SuviCa a Boulder-based company researching cancer treatments.

#### LEAD USER INTERFACE DESIGNER/DEVELOPER, PCGAMINGWIKI - 2013 - PRESENT

- Designed site iconography.
- Implemented a full website redesign in 2015 with improved functionality, responsive design for mobile users, and improved load times.



https://connorshea.github.io connor.james.shea@gmail.com

## Education

Colorado State University, Fort Collins, CO Expected May 2019

Bachelor of Science, Major: Computer Science

ThunderRidge High School, Highlands Ranch, CO Graduated May 2015

# Leadership

LEAD DESIGNER, "THE GROWL", HIGHLANDS RANCH, CO - 2013 - 2015

- Lead the design of my high school student newspaper, "The Growl", during my Junior and Senior year.
- Guided the paper through a page size change and associated redesign, including personally redesigning the logo and overall stylesheet.
- Conceptualized and designed multiple covers, as well as main story graphics.

### Skills

- Web Development HTML, CSS/SCSS, JavaScript (with jQuery), React.js, Ruby on Rails, Jekyll, Responsive Web Design
- Software Development Issue tracking, Git revision control, GitHub
- **Digital Design** Advanced usage of Adobe Illustrator, designing logos, website/software mockups
- **Graphic Design** Layout, passionate about typography, more "traditional" graphic design pieces, e.g. posters, infographics. I've filled multiple sketchbooks with interface sketches and logo concepts.